<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Marshall Moutenot]]></title>
  <link href="http://pewpewlasers.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://pewpewlasers.com/"/>
  <updated>2013-02-26T21:48:38-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://pewpewlasers.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Marshall Moutenot]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[mmoutenot@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlueCotton FTW]]></title>
    <link href="http://pewpewlasers.com/blog/2013/02/26/bluecotton-ftw/"/>
    <updated>2013-02-26T21:22:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://pewpewlasers.com/blog/2013/02/26/bluecotton-ftw</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This past weekend was <a href="http://www.tuftshackathon.com">Tuft’s second annual Hackathon</a>, a 24-hour event where students and mentors code and design projects. The event was the product of months of planning, and the last week was a sprint of emails, catering orders, and most importantly t-shirts.</p>

<p>We decided to order our t-shirts from the same company we did last year, <a href="http://bluecotton.com">BlueCotton</a>. Everything was going swimmingly until after a failed delivery attempt, UPS decided to reroute the shirts to Nashville, TN. As we watched our package move farther and farther away, UPS was of little help.</p>

<p>The day before the event, with no time to spare, we reached out to our customer representative at BlueCotton, Danyel. She had been aware of our desperate situation and decided to help us out. After a 2PM phone call the day before the event, BlueCotton reprinted all of our shirts and overnight shipped them from Kentucky to Boston. By 9:30AM the next day - the day of the event - they were at our front door and everyone looked fantastic.</p>

<p><img src="http://pewpewlasers.com/images/hackathon_shirts.png" alt="Tufts Hackathon Shirts" />
Photo credit: <a href="http://twitter.com/brennanjp">John Brennan</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bleep Bloop - Gur]]></title>
    <link href="http://pewpewlasers.com/blog/2013/01/03/bleep-bloop-gur/"/>
    <updated>2013-01-03T11:47:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://pewpewlasers.com/blog/2013/01/03/bleep-bloop-gur</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>For Christmas, my friend Jamie gave me an gift that nearly made my head explode
- his Maschine controller. I&#8217;ve been totally infatuated with it for the last few
  days. Here is a track I made last night, inspired by a
  bangin&#8217; beat Jamie made the other day.</p>

<iframe width="100%" height="166" scrolling="no" frameborder="no" src="http://w.soundcloud.com/player/?url=http%3A%2F%2Fapi.soundcloud.com%2Ftracks%2F73497454&amp;"></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Opportunity Cost]]></title>
    <link href="http://pewpewlasers.com/blog/2012/12/25/opportunity-cost/"/>
    <updated>2012-12-25T01:08:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://pewpewlasers.com/blog/2012/12/25/opportunity-cost</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>My degree, like most, comes with a litany of prescribed courses. I left all of
my required humanity, art and social science courses (unaffectionately called
HASS credits) for my senior year because, heck, I thought that sounded fun. I
would get all of my hard maths and computer science classes done, allowing me to
split my energy in the final year. I could spend half of my energy going to
school and the other half applying the knowledge I had hopefully gained from the
previous three years to side projects and part-time work.</p>

<p>So, in my second-to-last semester, one of the classes I chose was Introduction
To Economics. Why not? I was confident in my ability to solve single variable
equations, and I enjoyed a basic econmoics course I took in highschool. I
actually started to look forward to it.</p>

<p>Jump to the first day. I’m sitting down in class surrounded by a thousand
freshmen either playing Gangam-style Tetris or furiously scribbling the
lecturer’s words as if they were scripture. We started with the usual
formalities. Office hours, recitation (“Definitely go! These will be helpful!”).</p>

<p>My mind wandered to one of my side projects, <a href="http://app.snppi.com">Snappi</a>. I
was dying to reimplement the way in which I connected to different APIs. When I
zoned back in, the professor was talking about “Opportunity Cost”.</p>

<blockquote><p>op.por.tu.ni.ty cost</p>

<p>the loss of potential gain from other alternatives when on alternative is chosen</p></blockquote>

<p>I immediately stood up and marched towards the door. I never attended lecture or
recitation again.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
